[Piyarak Hospital]
Hey, how is Pun?
He's safe. How is Boat?
He's safe, too.
But the doctor wanted to check his brain.
- His brain?
- Sure, let's do it.
I'll take care of their medical bills.
I need to talk to the nurses.
I'll ask them about the rooms.
Okay.
Can I talk to you?
Come here.
What is it?
I just talked to the police.
They said
that they're also working on Ginny's case.
They asked me a lot of questions
about you and Ginny.
Like, were you two close?
Did you work together in many projects?
They also asked about Wee.
Why did they ask about Wee?
Ginny took her English courses in New York.
And it was the same time
that Wee was in the US.
Thai people fly to the US all the time.
Wee attended a seminar in LA,
I think he's safe.
I heard the makeup artists talking,
and they said that Ginny dated a politician.
I don't know who he was.
[Piyarak Hospital]
Thank you.
I took care of them already.
So, did the doctor check on you?
Oh my goodness!
I was worried about them
and I forgot about you.
You should go to see a doctor.
It's okay, I didn't hurt much.
It was just a few bruises.
- You should see a doctor.
- Yeah, you should.
And I want you to spend a night
at the hospital.
So you don't have to talk to the reporters.
Domino should talk to the reporters.
I will guide you on what you can say.
I don't want to be in news
quite often lately.
I'm campaigning at the moment.
My family doesn't want you
to get caught in any trouble.
Sure.
About the guy who came to rescue you...
His timing is just too perfect, isn't it?
Are you sure
that he has nothing to do with it?
From my experience, most of the time,
a hero doesn't always just appear like that.
I think it could be a marketing gimmick.
It's marketing.
Wee.
You really think
that he was working with the stalker?
Why would he do that for? It...
I just want to do a background check on him
to see if he has something to do with it.
If not, then fine.
I just started on my campaign
and anything could happen.
Sure.
Good.
Please take care of Eva.
You got it.
Let's see a doctor, come on.
I'll take care of her.
Is it hurting anywhere?
Please take care of Eva.
Give her the best special treatment.
Sure, thank you.
Mr. Weechana, please wait.
I am Police Captain Ekachai.
From Pathumwan Station?
You're taking care of Ginny's case?
Yes, sir.
I need to ask you a few questions, sir.
How can I contact you?
You can make an appointment
through my secretary.
I'm willing to cooperate.
But I wasn't there when Eva was attacked.
You should know about it.
With all due respect, sir,
I will be asking questions
regarding the death of Ginny.
This is not about Eva's case.
You might know Ginny from a different aspect.
And it could benefit her case.
I don't know what you are talking about,
but you can make an appointment.
- Hi.
- Hi, how are you doing?
Are you feeling better?
I'm okay.
Mr. Weechana will take care
of all your medical expenses.
- Thank you.
Let me know if you need anything.
Please take a look at our portfolio.
And... please consider letting us
work with you.
My friend is the best candidate,
since he was able to save you like that.
It's true. You could have been dead.
You didn't know the stalker
or had a deal with him before this, did you?
That's right.
We didn't know anything about the stalker.
No! That's not what I meant.
- I mean...
- Are you fucking serious?
Please calm down.
I mean it's hard to believe, right?
A stranger risked his life to save me.
You're talking about good things
like they're literally impossible.
It's really strange.
Listen, I don't know
how the hell you grew up.
But honestly, I feel sorry for you
if that's really how you see the world.
Seriously, you think we're so pathetic
that we do something that awful to you,
just to have you hire us?
That's fucking ridiculous!
Stop swearing, buddy.
What did you just say?
What did you say to me?
I said
that my friend and I are not pathetic enough
to do something horrible like that,
just to get you to hire us.
I know you said more than this.
Spill it out, all of it!
You really didn't get what is said?
- Pun, please?
- Yeah, I didn't get it.
A Thai person who likes to speak English
when he's mad,
people see that he has no manners.
If you want to say bad things about me,
say it in Thai, say it!
Fine, then listen to me.
I said that it is very strange
that you questioned
about people doing nice things to each other.
I said I didn't know how you grew up,
but I feel bad for you
for seeing the world like this.
I'll go back to my room.
You should get some rest.
I'll be back tomorrow.
Hey.
Are you hungry?
You want some rice
with chicken and gourd soup?
I like gourd.
Go ahead.
Pun.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
Seeing from your point of view,
you're not wrong for thinking that.
I understand
that the world isn't that wonderful.
Well...
can you tell me your strengths?
And your friend's?
Okay.
Well, I'm a chef,
and I got a degree in Sports Nutrition,
that is, nutrition and diet for athletes.
I cook the best healthy dishes.
I can make your body lean
while maintaining your curves with my food.
80% of body sculpting is based on your food.
I think you know that.
Sounds interesting.
My friend is a great personal trainer,
with great determination.
He is not as famous as others,
but he's very focused on his work.
Our skills can really benefit you.
So?
I'll think about it.
Look, you don't have to hire me.
But I think you should give Boat a chance.
He's really good at this.
I'll let you know tomorrow.
I said I will tell you tomorrow.
- Why are you following me?
- What?
Nope, I'm not following you.
My room is that way.
Hello, Auntie?
I'm doing fine, really.
I'm strong like a superhero, don't you know?
The nice guys saved me today,
they're so kind to me.
You don't have to come and see me.
I'll be home tomorrow.
Don't worry about me.
How could I not worry about you?
A man attempted to kill you?
And blood spilled all over your body
the other day.
You need to be sprayed with holy water.
When you're free,
I will take you to a temple.
Sure.
I'll let you know when I am free.
You should go to bed.
You need to wake up early tomorrow.
Okay.
Domino, can you look at their portfolio
one more time?
And check Boat's rate for me.
Only Boat?
He can barely move, he's like a robot.
Fine, the other guy's rate too.
He's interesting.
Got it. Both of them, right?
Yes! Ouch...
Sure, I'll handle it.
Talk to you later.
I'll look at your portfolio again
and I'll push your profile first, okay?
Thank you.
- Have you come up with the rate yet?
- Yes, I have.
I'll tell you the result later.
Get some rest and get well soon.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
I'm sorry about this.
It's okay.
- I should go, bye.
- Talk to you later.
Yes! We need the job, we will get the job.
Please, holy spirits at the gym.
We've shed our blood in your territory.
Give us a chance to wipe off that blood.
We will do a great job, please.
- Good morning.
You're up early? What's on your schedule?
Yeah, I need to see people in my district.
I want to see Eva if I'm done early.
How is she? She must be terrified.
She was faced with both Ginny's case,
and being attacked.
She handled it well.
She was lucky that she wasn't really hurt.
Someone was there to help her.
Did Eva know about you and Ginny?
I don't think so.
Good.
But I think the police know about it.
Who?
I'm not sure how much he knows.
I know that there were clips
from Ginny's stalkers.
They took videos of her all the time.
The police wanted to ask me questions
about Ginny too.
Give me the names.
Okay.
A little bit on this side.
So green.
You have a green thumb, ma'am.
Tell Weechai to come and see me.
Tell your son not to bring any girls home.
He couldn't get a room at a hotel?
I saw two girls leaving his room.
Two girls!
Our house isn't a cheap roadside motel.
I'll talk to him.
Morning, fam!
Stop right there. Don't come any closer.
I don't know who you slept with last night,
but it's disgusting.
I told your dad to lecture you about
bringing strangers back to our house.
If your dad can't make you stop this habit,
I will tell your girlfriend.
Grandma!
If she breaks up with you,
don't bother bringing another girl home.
Pie's parents are valuable to us,
in many ways.
You shouldn't upset them by sleeping around.
Wee! You, too.
Supoj's daughter is a better match for you.
You should stay away from Eva
and date her instead.
I have my reason for dating Eva.
We need more votes from the grassroots
and the middle class people.
I can relate more to these demographics
if I date Eva.
Will you keep campaigning
for the rest of your life?
You can break up with her
after you get the position.
You can't be with her forever,
or you'll lose other chances.
Wee is not someone's definite choice,
Grandma.
He is even harder to catch than me.
I was talking about
losing a chance with great women,
not some easy women to sleep with.
A woman whom you will marry,
needs to be accepted by me first.
She will be your legal wife,
a mother of your children,
and my great-grandchildren.
You need to stop bringing
your sleeping partners here.
We were not sleeping.
None of us got any sleep.
This is not funny.
People can't get in or out
of this house easily.
When Grandma gets frustrated,
she'd nag me about Eva constantly.
You need to stop.
Even if Eva did nothing,
she could never satisfy Grandma.
It has nothing to do with me.
Please.
Don't fucking mess with me.
What the fuck are you talking about?
I didn't even fucking mess with you.
Me? Messing with you? You're delusional.
Hello.
Any news from the forensic team?
We haven't received any official report yet.
They still need to run more tests.
But I asked around
and they said she could have been drugged.
Make sure you get the footage
from surveillance cameras in the event.
Get them all.
Don't let the police find out about it.
Let me know if you have any updates.
Hello, sir?
I will transfer Ginny's case to someone else.
Someone else?
Who are they?
They can work faster and close the case soon.
This case is causing damage to many people.
- They want it to finalize soon.
- But sir.
I wasn't too slow on this case.
I am focusing on...
Hello?
Did you get the autopsy report of Ginny?
Got it, I just want to know.
My case got transferred,
so I've got free time.
And it caught my attention.
Can you hurry up and send me the report?
Please help me on this.
Thank you.
Your blood pressure is normal.
I'm so excited to meet you in person.
Can I get a picture?
I'm not quite ready for a photo, maybe later.
Got it. Thanks anyway.
The doctor will see you this afternoon.
- Hello.
I'm so bored, I want to go home.
Sure. If the doctor says
you can be discharged, you can leave.
Nice smile.
Hey.
About your personal trainer,
I checked their profiles.
Actually, they're not bad.
The rate is more affordable
because they're not famous.
More importantly,
did you hear when Pun scolded us
in English fluently?
Why?
- What?
- Don't tell me...
Yeah.
Listen, he had lived overseas
since he was 16 years old.
His accent is so cool.
Also, he didn't look like the type
who'd chase the spotlight.
So he likely won't use your photos
to promote his service.
Do we really need to hire an English tutor?
You need to imitate his accent.
He can coach you how to say your lines.
You can practice by speaking with him
for three months.
To say it correctly.
Eva.
You really need a tutor for this.
I don't want any other tutors
to talk about this.
It will be a juicy piece of gossip for sure.
Fine.
Can you ask him to see
if he's okay with this?
Okay, my friend.
- What?
- Your accent still hasn't improved.
Mine is better than yours.
If I didn't have so much work to do,
I could be your tutor instead.
- Pun!
- Don't talk to me now.
Pun! Boat!
- You scared us!
- Well, you scared me too!
Are you okay?
You mean me or the floor?
- The floor.
He's funny, isn't he?
I brought you some food.
You must be sick of hospital food already.
Thank you.
Well, you shouldn't have.
Thank you for bringing us food.
- Go ahead.
- Let me see.
Wow! Pizza.
Normally, I don't eat carbs.
- But?
- But I will eat it to show you.
- Great.
- Let me see, which slice is the biggest?
I'll get this one.
Do you need some water?
- Yeah, that sounds good.
- I'll get some.
Thank you.
Let's say, if I hire you to be my trainers,
what will be your training plan?
Here's the plan.
It's like you're hiring two personal trainers.
I will focus on your workout plan,
to build your strength, flexibility,
and to get your body ready
for an action role.
Pun will be your nutritionist.
He can prepare your food
and design your diet plan.
You can eat three meals
and two snack breaks per day.
He can make really delicious healthy snacks.
You can have a look.
Okay, let me see. Thanks.
We came up with a plan
for your training program,
by combining with your diet plan
to sculpt and nourish your body.
[7 Day Healthy Meal Plan]
This is a sample of 7-day meal plan.
But I need to tell you that I'm very strict.
When I train you,
you need to believe me,
and listen to my instructions.
And you can't be stubborn.
I saw the plan that you followed earlier.
I know that you eat food
that you're not supposed to.
How did you know?
Muscles don't lie.
- Huh?
- I can tell from your muscles.
Boat could let it slide, but I won't.
I don't care if you will fire me.
I don't care who you are.
Your work is also my work.
If you wish to hire me,
you can't go off track.
Muscles don't lie.
Domino, follow me.
Okay.
Domino?
Right, your tablet.
Hurry up!
Okay, I'm coming.
Hey. What do you think of them?
I think they are honest.
They don't look like
the attention-seeking type.
And they're not cocky.
I prefer them over the others
because Pun can take care of my diet plan.
And one more thing.
You want him to be my English tutor.
Cool, shall we talk to them?
Yeah.
When Pun speaks,
his accent sounds like
when Wee talked to his friends.
I want him to teach me to speak like that,
and understand what they say.
Because I told Wee that I can speak English.
Oh my goodness!
That's so cool! You can speak too!
What's wrong?
That's the reason.
It'd be nice if Pun agrees to be my tutor.
I don't have to hire another tutor
and embarrass myself.
The news won't leak,
and nobody can start any rumors
that I'm not good at it.
You're right, I got it.
Shall I talk to them now?
Okay.
Eva.
Wee.
I didn't expect you to come.
Actually, my schedule was tight today,
but I need to come and see you.
I want to talk to you.
I haven't taken care of you lately.
And you kept encountering horrible incidents
one after another.
It's totally fine.
I understand.
We should wait until
things cool off for a bit.
I will make it up to you
until you get bored of me.
I can't wait.
I ran some background check
on the guys who saved you.
They are clean
and you have nothing to worry about.
That's great.
Can I...
Can I visit them?
I want to thank them in person.
Sure.
Thank you so much.
This gift is nothing
compared to what you did for Eva.
My friend should take all the credit.
- No problem.
- Thank you.
I heard that you just got back
from overseas, right?
- Yeah.
- Where did you just get back from?
New York, sir.
New York, I see.
Have you always been
a personal trainer since then?
Not really. Actually, I was...
Please excuse me.
Hello?
I see, alright.
Got it.
Okay, I will be there soon.
Alright.
I'm sorry, I really need to get back to work.
Actually, I have meetings all day,
but it was important for me
to come and see you.
Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
Eva.
We will host a party tomorrow at home,
and my dad would like you to join us.
Can you make it?
Yeah.
Are you sure?
Thank you so much.
I should get back to work.
- Okay.
- I'll talk to you later.
- See you later.
- Bye.
Sir?
I will ask them to edit the videos
for the press,
and select some photos for you to choose.
What are some intriguing topics to pitch?
For example, you feel really guilty
for being too focused in your work
that you had no time to take care of Eva.
I think you should find her a gift tonight
and post it on
your personal social media account.
Giving her a watch is also a good idea.
We can focus on giving her "more time".
Good, let's follow this plan.
- Got it, sir.
- Good.
Don't forget to edit his photos
before posting.
Ms. Eva?
Can I get a picture with you?
Sure.
One, two, three.
Thank you.
Hello, Weechana and Eva.
- Hello.
What did you talk about?
It seemed so much fun.
Eva just told us about shooting sets.
I thought being a star should be easy,
it turned out to be different than I thought.
Eva is able to tolerate
hardships in her life,
and I admire this trait about her.
I praised her all the time
about how far she has come.
She barely had anything in her life.
Have you met Nicole, Supoj's daughter?
She just graduated.
She came back to Thailand
for less than a month,
but foreign books and star agencies
already want her to join their team.
If she becomes a star, Eva,
please take care of her.
It will be my pleasure.
Let me know if you need my help.
Wee, can you introduce Nicole to Mr. Uthin?
Okay.
You should go with him.
If you'll excuse me.
Eva, please come with me.
I heard that you will be starring
in a foreign film.
That's right.
It's a huge studio.
They will shoot overseas
for 40% of the movie,
and the rest will be shot in Thailand.
Are you co-stars foreigners or Thai?
Both foreigners and Thai.
I see. Can you speak English with them?
Yeah.
I mean speaking fluently.
Having basic conversation skills
doesn't count, you know?
If you get the role
and you can't act that well,
it will be really terrible.
I will try my best.
Let's get something to eat. I'm hungry.
They look good together, don't you think?
In what way?
I think you know what I'm trying to tell you.
Don't act so innocent, confused, easy, stupid,
and ask me to repeat my question.
I really don't know
what you're talking about.
I am dating Wee.
But you asked me
if they looked good together.
So I need you to clarify it to me.
Good evening, Ms. Jit.
Good evening.
- Eva, hello.
- Hello.
Atchara, long time no see.
Enjoy the party.
Thanks.
If you want to hear it directly,
loud and clear,
then listen to me carefully.
Did you see how perfect they look together?
That's what I didn't see
when you two were together.
If it is just dating,
anyone can date him, including you.
When he needs to be serious
in a relationship,
not everyone can make the cut.
You should leave Weechana.
Otherwise, you will be exhausted,
and your effort will go to waste.
Because I don't like you.
I don't despise you or anything.
I'm just trying to protect what I built.
And I only select
what I think is the best choice,
the perfect match for my people.
It's like what you said to everyone.
That I can tolerate hardships in life.
I tell myself every single day
how blessed I am
to be standing here right now.
The others could be a better match for him
than me.
But I will prove to you
why your grandson picked me.
If you'll excuse me.
I know that you're strong enough
to walk by yourself.
Can I talk to you?